bollywoodhungama24.in 2013-02-05

# Privacy Policy | Bollywood & Hollywood Movies, Celebrities News & Gossips, Upcoming Movies, Reviews & Trailers, HD wallpapers

Privacy Policy for http://www.bollywoodhungama24.in/

The privacy of our visitors to http://www.bollywoodhungama24.in/ is important to us.

At http://www.bollywoodhungama24.in/, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information some advertisements companies receive and collect when you use and visit http://www.bollywoodhungama24.in/.

They never sell your personal information to third parties.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.

* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/

http://www.google.com/privacy.html

As mentioned in google privacy policy:

Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The

information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet

service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited

throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on http://www.bollywoodhungama24.in/ to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

* That All Content For Entertainment Purpose Who Visited This Site and provide latest news of bollywood to the users.

* “http://www.bollywoodhungama24.in/” is not Hosted Any vulgar or pornography images of celebrities, If you Want to remove any image about Copyright issue  then just Contact Us. These All Images are hosted on internet for information and news purpose only.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your

browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.

However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

http://www.bollywoodhungama24.in/ does not store any files listed on its server.

All posts are for informational purpose only and latset updates of bollywood.

Please Contact us On Our Email Address “contact@bollywoodhungama24.in”, if you found any content or image on this site about copyright issue.

This Website http://www.bollywoodhungama24.in/ is for entertainment purposes only.

Content may contain errors or inaccurate information, as it is based on entertainment news, gossips, wallpapers of celebs and personal opinions.

All images and videos that appear on this blog are copyright their respective owners.

If you own the rights to any of the images and do not wish them to appear on this site,Please Contact us On Our Email Address “contact@bollywoodhungama24.in” , and they will be removed as soon as possible.

Disclaimer

Actually we collect image from the various websites of internet, so if any image of this

sitehave any privacy policy or if anyone have any complain about any post, please feel free to contact with us. We will delete the offending post as soon as possible after the confirmation of the person who want to remove the post.

Just send an e-mail at: contact@bollywoodhungama24.in
